Guide to the A. Poulin Papers and BOA Editions Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 1997 Acquisition, 1951-1996; 3; 39.38; (44 boxes)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory, uncorrected proofs, undated; 2 (Box 104)
  - Various book sleeves, miscellaneous, undated (Box 104)
  - Patrick, William B.: These Upraised Hands, Book sleeve and manuscript galleys, 1995; 2 (Box 104)
  - Patrick, William B.: These Upraised Hands, page proofs and photographic materials for cover illustration, 1995 (Box 104)
  - X-ray of skull: Not used for Snodgrass, undated (Box 104)
  - "CAP VI. HMC. Correspondence", 1990-1995 (Box 105)
  - "[Al's copies of] New Poems [for CAP VI; Contents New and Old]", undated (Box 105)
  - "Reader's Reports/CAP and Questionnaire/ Suggestions/Reviews for Editor/Poulin", [1992-1994] (Box 105)
    Two separate files in folder.
  - CAP Photo/miscellaneous Notes, [1990-1995] (Box 105)
  - New Poets, undated (Box 105)
  - Revised notes and biblios./Completed biblios/NOTES/CAP VI/The Big Guy's Copies (Al), undated (Box 105)
  - CAP V Galleys, circa 1991 (Box 105)
  - Newspaper: Lewiston Journal/Magazine Section; news clippings; Report and Recommendations, December 1, 1970 (w/ A. Poulin, Chairman), 1964, 1970 December (Box 105)
  - Bills, receipts, undated; 3 (Box 105)
  - Autograph book, undated (Box 105)
  - St. Bernadette School: memory book, undated (Box 105)
  - Award notice to Al Poulin from St. Francis College, Office of the Dean, undated (Box 105)
  - Diploma, Al Poulin, from St. Bernadette School., 1951 June 17 (Box 105)
  - Cover for diploma, Al Poulin, from Eymard Preparatory Seminary, Class of 1955 (Box 105)
  - Cover for diploma and Program for Ninety-Second Annual Commencement of Loyola University, 1962 June 7 (Box 105)
  - Id. card from the University of Iowa (MFA in English), 1968 June 7 (Box 106)
  - Box of namecards and 4-bk boxed set; St. Andrew Daily Missal, undated (Box 106)
  - Envelope, Shell Oil, checks and receipts, 1969 (Box 106)
  - SFC Check Stubs 1968. Checking Account Deposit Slips., undated (Box 106)
  - Various labeled envelopes with corresponding deposits, bills and receipts, [1969-1970]; 2 (Box 106)
  - Envelope from the Durham Trust Co. (statements of accounts); bills and receipts, [1965-1966] (Box 106)
  - Envelope from the First National Bank, statements, bills and receipts, [1968] (Box 106)
  - Labeled envelopes with corresponding bills and receipts, [1965-1970]; 8 (Box 106)
  - Labeled envelopes with corresponding bills and receipts, [1965-1970]; 4 (Box 107)
  - Second envelope from the Durham Trust Co., [1966] (Box 107)
  - Envelope, "TAX 1968" including various folders: books and magazines, electricity, miscellaneous royalties, etc., 3 (Box 107)
  - Labeled envelopes, [1966-1968]; 3 (Box 107)
  - Miscellaneous personal correspondence and other various miscellaneous material, 1966-1968; undated; 5 (Box 107)
  - Bills and receipts, [1966-1970]; 3 (Box 107)
  - Correspondence and other various miscellaneous material, [1964-1968]; 11 (Box 108)
  - Third Durham Trust Co. envelope, [1965-1966] (Box 108)
  - Travel information, and related papers, [1964-1967; undated]; 2 (Box 108)
  - Rejections and various submissions, [1992-1993]; 9 (Box 108)
  - Rejections and various submissions, [1992-1993]; 12 (Box 109)
  - News clippings, articles, reviews, etc. including the Jul/Aug '92 American Poetry Review, 1992 (Box 109)
  - Magazines, poetry reviews: CONTACT/II Spring '92 and POETRY April '92, 1992 (Box 109)
  - Magazines, poetry reviews: DAKA Magazine Sep '91 and Multicultural Rvw. Apr '92, [1991-1992] (Box 109)
  - News clippings, articles, reviews, etc. including Poetry Flash May '92, [1991-1992] (Box 109)
  - Tar River Poetry: 2 issues. Fall '91, Spring '92, [1991-1992] (Box 109)
  - MD (Medical Directors Magazine): 2 issues. Nov '91; Publisher's Weekly: 1 issue. Jun '92, [1991-1992] (Box 109)
  - DAKA Magazine: 2 issues. Summer '91; MD: 1 issue. Sep '92., [1991-1992] (Box 109)
  - Various submissions, [1994-1995]; 5 (Box 109)
  - Hébert: Day Has No Equal But Night, Galley pages and thumbnail., undated (Box 109)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks, Extra type., undated (Box 109)
  - Hébert: Day Has No Equal But Night, Galley Proofs, [1994]; 2 (Box 109)
  - Sample book cover for Barton Sutter's The Book of Names: New and Selected Poems, undated (Box 109)
  - Addonizio: The Philosopher's Club, uncorrected proofs and K.A.'s corrections, [1993-1994]; 4 (Box 110)
  - Addonizio: copy edited manuscript, undated (Box 110)
  - Addonizio: The Philosopher's Club, page proofs, [1993] (Box 110)
  - Addonizio: The Philosopher's Club, uncorrected proofs, [1994] (Box 110)
  - Nye manuscript: corrected. Red Suitcase. Photo ready master, [1994] (Box 110)
  - Nye: Red Suitcase, uncorrected galleys, [1994] (Box 110)
  - Nye: Red Suitcase, etc. 3 corrected proofs: Al's hand. Naomi's hand with letter, BOA copy, [1994]; 3 (Box 110)
  - Nye: Red Suitcase, uncorrected galleys, [1994] (Box 110)
  - Meyer, Michael: Poetry: An Introduction published by Bedford Bks of St. Martin's Press, Boston., 1995 (Box 110)
  - Authors' submissions and correspondence, [1994-1995]; 12 (Box 110)
  - Mattawa, Khaled A.: Ismailia Eclipse, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 110)
  - Hales, Corrine: Approaching Intimacy, manuscript copy, undated (Box 110)
  - Slavitt, David R.: Sixty Psalms of David, bound manuscript copy, 1994 (Box 110)
  - Dassanowsky-Harris, Robert: Telegrams from the Metropole: Collected Poetry 1980-1995, bound manuscript copy (Box 110)
  - Kremers, Carolyn: A Moose Must Get Very Close, manuscript copy, 1995 (Box 111)
  - Barnstone, Willis, 1994, undated; 2 (Box 111)
    Folder 1: 2 chapbooks, bound manuscript copies, Grim Book: Poems and Diary of a Dog: 101 Solitudes
    Folder 2: 1 chapbook, bound manuscript copy: The Secret Reader: 5 Histories: 501 Sonnets
  - Rick Lyon: WTNH-TV 8 news story, 1994 September; YCALMSS635_0002; 1; 00:04:26 (Box 134)
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copy may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
  - The Griffin: Vol. 42, No. 8, June '92, 1992 June (Box 111)
  - Drake, Barbara: Writing Poetry: 2nd edition, published by Harcourt Brace College Publishers, 1994 (Box 111)
  - Hopkins, Lee Bennett: Hand in Hand: An American History through Poetry, 1994 (Box 111)
  - BOA Editions, Ltd.: Checklist 1977-1990 (Box 111)
  - Miller, Jane: Working Time: Essays on Poetry, Culture, and Travel, 1992 (Box 111)
  - Norton, Spring 1995 [catalogue of titles/booklist], 1994 (Box 111)
  - Duhamel, Denise: It's My Body [chapbook] and various writings and submissions, [1992-1993] (Box 111)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: Not A Stranger, Version #1, 1993 (Box 111)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: Song: Poems, page proofs, manuscript copy, 1995 (Box 111)
  - Paola, Suzanne: Various manuscripts, [1991-1992] (Box 111)
  - Patrick, William: Family Stories: A Series of Poems, undated (Box 111)
  - BOA Editions Ltd: Christmas Party invitations, 1994 December (Box 111)
  - Mead, Jane: House of Poured-Out Waters, 1994 (Box 111)
  - Patrick, William: 18 Monologues: Poems and Dreams When We're Not Asleep, 1994; 2 (Box 111)
  - Book Sales and Distribution: Consortium Spring and Summer '95: New Titles Catalog, [1995] (Box 111)
  - Snodgrass, W.D.: The Führer Bunker: The Complete Cycle: Poems. Uncorrected proofs, manuscript copy, 1995 (Box 112)
  - Rejected manuscript and folder with empty envelope, 1994 (Box 112)
  - Personal correspondence, miscellaneous, [1993-1994]; 2 (Box 112)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks: Poems Selected and New; Page proofs, manuscript copy, [1992-1993] (Box 112)
  - BOA: '93 Mailing Log, [1992-1993] (Box 112)
  - Nye: Red Suitcase materials, 1994; 4 (Box 112)
    Folder 1: 3 computer diskettes (removed); author photo
    Folder 2: Red Suitcase: Poems, manuscript copy
    Folder 3: book covers, miscellaneous
    Folder 4: Red Suitcase: Poems, manuscript copy
  - Folder entitled, "California," miscellaneous, [1992] (Box 112)
  - Cover art, various photographic versions, undated (Box 112)
  - Various manuscript materials, miscellaneous, [1994] (Box 112)
  - Various submissions and related correspondence, [1990-1992]; 4 (Box 112)
  - Sutter, Barton; Lee, Li-Young: various materials, [1989-1996]; 4 (Box 112)
  - Addonizio, Kim; Shoaf, Diann Blakely: various materials, [1991-1993]; 5 (Box 113)
  - Lyon, Rick; Costanzo, Gerald: various materials, [1991-1993]; 4 (Box 113)
  - Hébert, Anne: Day Has No Equal But Night, various materials, [1994]; 2 (Box 113)
  - Authors' submissions, correspondence, [1993]; 6 (Box 113)
  - Bond, Bruce: Feast of the Seven Sorrows, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 113)
  - Mozon, Nadine: Serendipity, bound manuscript copy, 1993 October (Box 113)
  - Author's submissions, correspondence, [1992-1993]; 9 (Box 113)
  - Kleinschmidt, Edward: Testacoda, manuscript copy, undated (Box 113)
  - Kleinschmidt, Edward: Speed of Life, manuscript copy, undated (Box 113)
  - Chin, Marilyn: The Phoenix Gone, The Terrace Empty, bound manuscript copy, [1992 September] (Box 113)
  - Duhamel, Denise: Girl Soldier, manuscript copy, undated (Box 113)
  - Nguyen Khac Truong: The Plot of Land with Many Ghosts and Plenty of People, translation by Phan Thanh Hao and Sarah Bales, bound manuscript copy, 1992 (Box 114)
  - Personal correspondence, miscellaneous, [1985-1993]; 2 (Box 114)
  - Newspaper, Pacific Sun, with article on Dorianne Laux, 1993 December (Box 114)
  - Hébert, Anne: Day Has No Equal But Night: Poems, translation by A. Poulin, Jr., signed manuscript copy, [1993] (Box 114)
  - Hébert: Various materials, undated (Box 114)
  - Mailers: Sutton cover, Lyon Bell 8 cover, undated (Box 114)
  - Snodgrass, W.D.: The Führer Bunker: bound manuscript copies, undated; 2 (Box 114)
  - Snodgrass, W.D.: Each in His Season, typescript, manuscript copy, undated (Box 114)
  - Weekly World News, August 1994 issue, 1994 August (Box 114)
  - BOA mailings, including The Griffin News from BOA Editions, Ltd., undated (Box 114)
  - Various BOA mailings and publications, undated (Box 114)
  - "Rejections Box 30", [1994] (Box 114)
  - Various submissions, correspondence, [1989-1994]; 23 (Box 114)
  - Bhanu Kapil: Prose-poetry from Le Livre Pour Toi by Marguerite Burnat-Provins, manuscript copy, undated (Box 115)
  - Harrison, Jeffrey: Brief History of an Atlas, manuscript copy, 1994 (Box 115)
  - Breskin, David: Fresh Kills, manuscript copy, 1994 August (Box 115)
  - Mock, Jeff: The Body of Losses and Lives, 1994 March (Box 115)
  - Hill, Perrie: Echoes over Water, manuscript copy, [1994?] (Box 115)
  - Snodgrass, W.D.: The Führer Bunker, bound manuscript copies, undated; 3 (Box 115)
  - Snodgrass: The Führer Bunker, various materials, 1995; 8 (Box 115)
  - Snodgrass: The Führer Bunker, cover proofs, [1995] (Box 115)
  - Foerster, Richard and Snodgrass, W.D.: various manuscript materials, undated; 5 (Box 115)
  - Snodgrass: Envelope titled, "BOA BOYZ": "Al's corrections/ Corrected pages only", 1995 (Box 115)
  - BOA Führer Bunker cover design. X-Ray, [1995 January] (Box 115)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: The Führer Bunker: The Complete Cycle, [1995]; 4 (Box 115)
  - News From BOA Editions Ltd. BOA Reviews, [1994-1995]; 5 (Box 115)
  - Addonizio: The Philosopher's Club, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 116)
  - Lyon, Rick: Bell 8, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 116)
  - Cendrars, Blaise: Christmas at the Four Corners of the Earth, translation by Bertrand Mathieu, bound manuscript copy, 1994 (Box 116)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard: Wordworks: Poems Selected and New, bound manuscript copy, 1993 November (Box 116)
  - Snodgrass, W. D. In envelope entitled, "Song" The Führer Bunker: The Complete Cycle, manuscript copy, 1995; 4 (Box 116)
  - Nye, Naomi Shihab: various materials including uncorrected proofs, 1994-1995; 2 (Box 116)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: various materials including uncorrected proofs, 1994-1995; 2 (Box 116)
  - Various authors' materials, including page proofs and manuscript copy of Dorianne Laux's What We Carry; poems by Peter Makuck; Anne Hébert, Day Has No Equal..., [1993] (Box 116)
  - Makuck, Peter: Worldwise by Catlight, manuscript copy, [1994 December] (Box 116)
  - Slavitt, David: Essay, "The Year in Poetry, 1994", [1995 June] (Box 116)
  - Issue of Minnesota Monthly Feb 1995 and poetry fliers, [1995 February] (Box 116)
  - Lannan Foundation info., undated (Box 116)
  - Envelope from "JMS Enterprises, Inc.," back labeled "Rejections", [1993 August]; 2 (Box 116)
  - Levy, Robert J.: In the Century of Small Gestures, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 116)
  - Lopez, Sam: Draft of 1st or 2nd novel, Something Called Honor, selections, undated (Box 116)
  - Minerd, Jeff: Don't Save Grandpa and Other Stories, unbound manuscript copy, 1991 May (Box 116)
  - Anghelaki-Rooke, Katerina: In This House, selections, unbound manuscript copy, undated (Box 116)
  - Lee, Li-Young: First Draft of Autobiography, Aug 1991, unbound manuscript copy, 1991 August (Box 116)
  - Schwartz, Delmore: Shenandoah and Other Verse Plays, bound manuscript copy, [1992] (Box 116)
  - Masters/Archive. Bly Gratitude Masters, [1993] (Box 116)
  - Page proofs for Schwartz, Delmore: Shenandoah and Other Verse Plays, unbound manuscript copy, 1992 (Box 117)
  - Patrick, William: Hurry Back to Memphis, A Scenario and Brand New Me, A Screenplay [2 manuscript copies, 1 unbound, 1 bound], undated (Box 117)
  - Various miscellaneous correspondence, selections of poems and Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, Poems, unbound manuscript copy, undated (Box 117)
  - Various authors' submissions, [1992-1993; undated]; 7 (Box 117)
  - Various authors' submissions, miscellaneous author photos, BOA correspondence, [1994-1995]; 20 (Box 117)
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn: miscellaneous BOA correspondence, various materials, [1994-1995] (Box 117)
  - Bell, Marvin: miscellaneous BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 117)
  - Dove, Rita: manuscript of poems from Mother Love, including publishing and repro. contract, [1994-1995]; 2 (Box 117)
  - Bly, Robert: miscellaneous BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 117)
  - Stryk, Lucien: miscellaneous BOA correspondence; Letters to a Stranger: Poems by Thomas James, bound manuscript copy, [1994-1995]; [circa 1973] (Box 117)
  - Williams, C. K.: New Poems, repro. dupes., unbound manuscript copy, and BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 117)
  - Wright, Charles: 2 unbound manuscript copies. Chickamauga, 1994 July 11 (Box 117)
  - Stern, Gerald: selections from manuscript entitled Odd Mercy, unbound manuscript copy and BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Simpson, Louis: BOA correspondence and unbound manuscript copy, New Poems, [1994] (Box 118)
  - Piercy, Marge and Snodgrass, W. D.: BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Nye, Naomi Shihab: selections, unbound manuscript copy, Apr 1995 and BOA correspondence (Box 118)
  - Rich, Adrienne: BOA correspondence and selections, unbound manuscript copy, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Merwin, William S.: BOA correspondence and The Vixen, unbound manuscript copy, undated (Box 118)
  - Manuscript packet, with beginning sheet titled, "Books by James Merrill", [1995] (Box 118)
  - Matthews, William: BOA correspondence and selections, unbound manuscript copy from Time and Money, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Levertov, Denise: BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Various authors' submissions and BOA correspondence, [1994-1995]; 10 (Box 118)
  - Kinnell, Galway: BOA correspondence; unbound manuscript copy, Imperfect Thirst, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Hogan, Linda: BOA correspondence, article "Hearing Voices" in The Writer on her Work, other related papers; author photo, [1994-1995]; 3 (Box 118)
  - Ignatow, David: BOA correspondence, poetry selections, and untitled bound manuscript copy, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Bly, Robert: Meditations on the Insatiable Soul: Poems, unbound manuscript copy, [1994] (Box 118)
  - Ferlinghetti and Ginsberg, BOA correspondence, [1994] (Box 118)
  - Harper, Michael S. BOA correspondence and Honorable Amendments: Poems, bound manuscript copy c. 1995 (Box 118)
  - Hass, Robert. BOA correspondence and poetry selections, unbound manuscript copy, [1994-1995]; 2 (Box 118)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: BOA correspondence and uncorrected proofs for Bruise Theory: Poems, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Knott, Bill: Book mockup of The Quicken Tree: Poems and BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Patrick, William: Uncorrected proofs for These Upraised Hands: Poems and 2 unbound manuscript copies, Who All Killed Cock Robin: A Play, [1995] (Box 118)
  - Pamphlet on SpaceArc, various inquiries, submissions and BOA correspondence, [1994-1995] (Box 118)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory, copy- edited manuscript copy, [1992-1993] (Box 119)
  - Knott, Bill: The Quicken Tree, 2 copies, uncorrected proofs; 1 edited manuscript copy, [1995] (Box 119)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: unbound manuscript copy of Not A Stranger, [1995] (Box 119)
  - Issue of The Bloomsbury Review, 1995 July/August (Box 119)
  - Patrick, William: These Upraised Hands: Poems, unbound manuscript copy, [1995] (Box 119)
  - Piccione, Anthony: For the Kingdom, unbound manuscript copy, 1992 October (Box 119)
  - Di Pasquale, Emanuel: Di Pasquale manuscripts: rejected, 1994 September (Box 119)
  - Envelope entitled, "Takes '94" including BOA pamphlets, checklists, backlists and other related publications, [1994] (Box 119)
  - Envelope entitled, "Staff Reports", [1994-1995] (Box 119)
  - Ward, Thom: A Little Crazier Than the Maples, unbound manuscript copy, [1994] (Box 119)
  - Various authors' submissions, miscellaneous correspondence, [1993-1995]; 5 (Box 119)
  - Personal correspondence, [1992-1997?] (Box 119)
  - Various authors' submissions, [1994]; 6 (Box 119)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: unbound manuscript copy of Song, uncorrected proofs, [1994]; 2 (Box 120)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: working manuscript copy, undated (Box 120)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: unbound manuscript copy, Song: Poems, [1995] (Box 120)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: unbound manuscript copy, Song: Poems. Foul proofs., [1995] (Box 120)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: unbound manuscript copy, Song: Uncorrected proofs., [1994] (Box 120)
  - Envelope entitled, "Permissions", undated (Box 120)
  - "Archive. Old Permissions materials", undated (Box 120)
  - Lyon, Rick: miscellaneous. Various materials relating to Bell 8, [1994-1995] (Box 120)
  - Mostly Snodgrass, W. D.: miscellaneous, [1994] (Box 120)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, cover art images, undated (Box 120)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: The Führer Bunker, final version, undated; 3 (Box 120)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: acknowledgment pages, book copy original of Song, [1994] (Box 120)
  - Kelly, Brigit Pegeen: Song, galleys, [1994]; 2 (Box 120)
  - Appelbaum, Samuel: Enfleurage, unbound manuscript copy, 1994 December; 2 (Box 120)
  - Witte, John: Yonder, unbound manuscript copy, 1994 December (Box 120)
  - Kelly, J. Patrick: The Universe Waits, unbound manuscript copy, 1994 October (Box 120)
  - Perricone, C.: Justified Lies, unbound manuscript copy, 1994 September (Box 120)
  - Willis, Dawn Diez: The Brilliance of Flesh, unbound manuscript copy, 1994 December (Box 120)
  - Hazners, Dainis: Vecama: A Journal Poem, bound manuscript copy, 1994 November (Box 120)
  - Bond, Bruce: Radiography, bound manuscript copy, 1994 November (Box 120)
  - Sorrell, J. E.: Everything, unbound manuscript copy and related materials, 1994 September (Box 120)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: The Führer Bunker, binder notebook; bound manuscript copy; next- to-final version, 1994 October (Box 120)
  - "Snodgrass: Each in His Season. Masters Masters Masters" including final proofs; and "Snodgrass: Each in His Season. Galleys/Masters", [1993-1994?]; 2 (Box 121)
  - Packet labeled, "Orig. ms. with comments by Poulin and resp. by Snodgrass": copy of Each in His Season, undated (Box 121)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season: Poems, uncorrected proofs, 1993 (Box 121)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard: Wordworks: Poems Selected and New, 2 working manuscript copies, [1992]; 2 (Box 121)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard: Wordworks, original unbound manuscript, [undated?] (Box 121)
  - Costanzo, Gerald: Nobody Lives on Arthur Godfrey Boulevard, bound manuscript copy, [undated] (Box 121)
  - Lee, Li-Young: The Winged Seed: A Memoir. Autobiography, 4th version with letter, [undated] (Box 121)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard: Wordworks: Poems Selected and New, bound manuscript copy, 1993 November (Box 121)
  - Lee, Li-Young: "R". Autobiography, 3rd version, 1993 September (Box 121)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: Not A Stranger, bound manuscript copy, original version, undated (Box 121)
  - Crosby, William H., translation: The Poems of Catullus, bound manuscript copy, [1991-1992] (Box 121)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, manuscript copy, 1993 (Box 121)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, manuscript copy. Foul galleys., 1993 May (Box 121)
  - Laux, Dorianne: What We Carry, unbound manuscript copy and set of corrections, 1993 September (Box 122)
  - Hébert, Anne: Day Has No Equal But Night, bound manuscript copy, translated by A. Poulin, Jr., 1993 (Box 122)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, "Galley proofs, not final", 1993 April (Box 122)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, "Gallies/Early set", 1993 December (Box 122)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, "Typescript," copy, 1993 March (Box 122)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, "Cover and Jacket Proofs", undated (Box 122)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: Each in His Season, Galley Proofs w/ corrections (Snodgrass' in red pen) Richard Foerster's in blue, [1993] (Box 122)
  - Bly, Robert: Gratitude to Old Teachers, Assorted page proofs, undated (Box 122)
  - Bly, Robert: Gratitude to Old Teachers, typescript from DISC (2 copies). Unbound uncorrected proof, [1993] (Box 122)
  - Bly, Robert: Gratitude to Old Teachers, Final proofs of masters. Xerox of cover proof. Assorted extra proof pages, [1993] (Box 122)
  - Bly, Robert: Gratitude to Old Teachers, galley proofs with corrections, [1993] (Box 122)
  - Miscellaneous BOA correspondence and manuscript, [1992-?] (Box 122)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory, two (2) copyedited versions, unbound manuscript copies, [1995]; 2 (Box 122)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory: Poems, uncorrected proofs, bound manuscript copy, 1995 (Box 122)
  - Cendrars, Blaise: Christmas at the Four Corners of the Earth, translation by Bertrand Mathieu, bound manuscript copy, [1994 June] (Box 122)
  - News from BOA Editions Ltd., Spring/ Summer 1995 (Box 122)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory, Unbound manuscript copy and corrections, miscellaneous materials relating to the manuscript, [1995] (Box 122)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory, Unbound manuscript copy. "Out sheets and foul proofs", [1995] (Box 122)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory: Poems, Unbound manuscript copy and related materials, [1995] (Box 122)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: The Führer Bunker, The Complete Cycle. Unbound manuscript copy, [1995] (Box 122)
  - Piccione, Anthony: For the Kingdom: Poems. Unbound manuscript copy with corrections, [1992 October] (Box 122)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence with Kim Stafford (fax and letter) and bound copy of "Consortium: Book Sales and Distribution. Fall and Winter 94-95", 1994-1995 (Box 122)
  - "Halftone and C/F Bar code Negs/ BOA Editions", [1993-1995] (Box 123)
  - Patrick, William B.: The Island of Birds: Poems, Unbound manuscript copy, [1995] (Box 123)
  - Piccione, Anthony: For the Kingdom: Poems, Unbound manuscript copy with envelope marked "Tony/corrections", [1995] (Box 123)
  - BOA Editions, Ltd. Fall/Winter 1995, New Titles and Complete Backlist (Box 123)
  - Patrick, William B.: Dreams When We're Not Asleep: Poems. Unbound manuscript copy. Knott, Bill: page proofs, manuscript copy., undated (Box 123)